<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>FullyFaired.com - Sports Bike Stuff | FullyFaired.com - Sports Bike Stuff</title>
        <link>/</link>
        <description>FullyFaired.com - Sports Bike Stuff | FullyFaired.com - Sports Bike Stuff</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 21:57:40 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
                <title>Posts</title>
                <link>/posts/</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 21:57:40 +0800</pubDate><guid>/posts/</guid>
                <description></description>
            </item><item>
                <title>About FullyFaired.com</title>
                <link>/about/</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 11:04:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid>
                <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hi-everyone&#34;&gt;Hi everyone!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m JR and I am the guy behind fullyfaired.com. I&amp;rsquo;ve been riding for over 10 years now and have found my home on sportbikes. I currently ride a ZX6R J1, which is the perfect mix of comfort and sport for my daily needs. On this site I have lots of information regarding ownership, tips, tricks and things that will hopefully answer your basic questions about riding a sportbike for daily use, and trips away. I have traveled parts of Europe and done several overnighters or weekends away riding and am always happy to share my knowledge for new comers and people planning their first trips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was a bit late to bikes really - my love for cars was most prominent growing up, loved the mid 90s Japanese turbo cars and eventually owned a Celica GT4 which was fantastic. But by my early twenties I&amp;rsquo;d started to take much more of an interest in 2 wheels, mostly stemming from watching some cracking MotoGP races. At the time it was much more interesting than F1, seemed more dangerous and had some serious rivalries going on. What was even better was the potential for lots of different winners and crazy overtakes, and not just a parade around a circuit with no overtaking. It really got me wanting to get my license and start riding. I managed to get to Donnington to watch one year whjen James Toseland finished 5th if I recall, behind Rossi who had fallen off once and in the pouring rain. The 250s and 125s as they were then were great to watch too. At the end the crowd rushed the track and JT barely made it back - missing boots gloves etc. If they could I&amp;rsquo;m sure they&amp;rsquo;d have had most of the bike away!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;bike-history&#34;&gt;Bike History:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aprilia RS125 full power  - (just don&amp;rsquo;t do it)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honda XR125 - which I passed my test on&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Susuki GS500 - dull as but served a purpose&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honda VFR750 - loads of issues but great bike&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kawasaki ZX6R J1 - a perfect mix for me right now&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bike Future:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who knows?! I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying the ZX6R right now so will hold onto that for another year or so. Going forward though I&amp;rsquo;d love to own, in no particular order:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fireblade 954&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;KTM Duke 690&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Triumph Street Triple&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            </item><item>
                <title>Privacy policy</title>
                <link>/privacypolicy/</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 11:04:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>/privacypolicy/</guid>
                <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-website-address-is-httpfullyfairedcom&#34;&gt;Our website address is: &lt;a href=&#34;http://fullyfaired.com&#34;&gt;http://fullyfaired.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-personal-data-we-collect-and-why-we-collect-it&#34;&gt;What personal data we collect and why we collect it&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;comments&#34;&gt;Comments&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://automattic.com/privacy/&#34;&gt;https://automattic.com/privacy/&lt;/a&gt;. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;media&#34;&gt;Media&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contact forms&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;cookies&#34;&gt;Cookies&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select &amp;ldquo;Remember Me&amp;rdquo;, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;embedded-content-from-other-websites&#34;&gt;Embedded content from other websites&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;analytics&#34;&gt;Analytics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;who-we-share-your-data-with&#34;&gt;Who we share your data with&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-long-we-retain-your-data&#34;&gt;How long we retain your data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;what-rights-you-have-over-your-data&#34;&gt;What rights you have over your data&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;where-we-send-your-data&#34;&gt;Where we send your data&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            </item><item>
                <title></title>
                <link>/disclaimer/</link>
                <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/disclaimer/</guid>
                <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;disclaimer&#34;&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FullyFaired.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.co.uk.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            </item></channel>
</rss>
