<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gear on FullyFaired.com - Sports Bike Stuff</title>
    <link>/tags/gear/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gear on FullyFaired.com - Sports Bike Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 21:57:40 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/gear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kriega US-30 Drypack Review</title>
      <link>/2019/12/kriega-us-30-drypack-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 21:57:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/12/kriega-us-30-drypack-review/</guid>
      <description>Kriega US-30 Drypack Review I’ve been thinking a lot about sorting out some more trips for this year. I didn’t manage to get out and about as much as I’d have liked to last year, so I want to get something organised soon. I’d really like to do a solo camping trip and I’ve started thinking about what I’d need to take. This got me thinking about how much stuff I can fit in my US30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorbike Ground Anchors – Reviews, Fitting and Using</title>
      <link>/2019/02/ground-anchors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 21:57:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/02/ground-anchors/</guid>
      <description>Since I moved to a new house with a garage, I started looking at sorting out security for my ZX6R. Previously it lived outside under a cover, tucked away in a private gated car park, but now even though it’s behind a garage door I think it’s always worth doing everything you can to deter potential thieves. That’s where a good ground anchor can help.
It’s a relatively inexpensive way to add another level of security making it all that bit harder for someone to take your pride and joy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>