<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maintenance on FullyFaired.com - Sports Bike Stuff</title>
    <link>/tags/maintenance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Maintenance on FullyFaired.com - Sports Bike Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 21:57:40 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/maintenance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Buying a Budget Sports bike – Things to know</title>
      <link>/2018/08/buying-a-budget-sportsbike/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 21:57:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/buying-a-budget-sportsbike/</guid>
      <description>Owning a budget sports bike can be an incredibly rewarding experience and I recommend everyone who enjoys riding delve into sports bikes at least once in their lives. These days you can get a lot of bike for your cash and picking the right one can often be very difficult. Whether it’s your first time buying a budget sports bike or if you’re getting your second or more this list below may help you when purchasing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Does My Motorcycle Battery Keep Draining?</title>
      <link>/2018/07/battery-draining/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 21:57:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/battery-draining/</guid>
      <description>Today I’m going to go through a few points and tips as to help explain what might be causing your battery to go flat and how to prolong the life of your battery and bike electrical system. I have first hand experience having previously owned a mid-90s Honda VFR750 which had charging problems, even causing me to (almost) get stuck in Belgium. Hondas from that era are notorious for reg/rec issues and there are countless internet posts about them, mine was no different – however after some research and going through the points below I was able to identify and replace the problem parts and fit in a voltmeter for early warning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Your Throttle Free Play</title>
      <link>/2018/05/setting-throttle-free-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 21:57:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/setting-throttle-free-play/</guid>
      <description>It’s important to get the throttle free play correct as it will improve responsiveness and the ability to ride smoothly. The throttle is one of the most important controls your bike has so it’s got to be precise to enable you to ride properly. Generally manufacturers recommend around 2-3mm of travel before the cable pulls. This means that when you fully close the throttle expect it to have this amount of free play before it engages – too much and you wont be able to ride smoothly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>