<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sports Bikes on FullyFaired.com - Sports Bike Stuff</title>
    <link>/categories/sports-bikes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sports Bikes on FullyFaired.com - Sports Bike Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 11:57:40 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/sports-bikes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorbike Camping – Best Tent?</title>
      <link>/2019/08/sportsbike-camping-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 11:57:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/08/sportsbike-camping-trip/</guid>
      <description>I am an avid camper and rider but only recently began mixing the two. Camping for me is historically been large tents and lots of gear – cooking equipment, entertainment; everything I thought I could ever possibly need would get chucked into the back of the estate car and off we went.
However that’s not really viable when you’re on two wheels. Space is a premium so gear must be slimmed down and match the required criteria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Quest for Power: Is more BHP always better?</title>
      <link>/2019/07/quest-for-more-bhp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 21:57:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/07/quest-for-more-bhp/</guid>
      <description>It’s an interesting paradigm when talking about power figures, and what they actually mean to the vast majority of us. The fact that power is a comparable measure of a bikes performance leads to lots of debate and potentially discarding bikes as they have slightly less power than the competitor. If we take the earliest Fireblades, which had around 111 hp, and compare to now the 2019 model is pushing 171hp – this begs the question, have we gone too far?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>