<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Luggage on FullyFaired.com - Sports Bike Stuff</title>
    <link>/categories/luggage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Luggage on FullyFaired.com - Sports Bike Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 21:57:40 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/luggage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kriega US-30 Drypack Review</title>
      <link>/2019/12/kriega-us-30-drypack-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 21:57:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/12/kriega-us-30-drypack-review/</guid>
      <description>Kriega US-30 Drypack Review I’ve been thinking a lot about sorting out some more trips for this year. I didn’t manage to get out and about as much as I’d have liked to last year, so I want to get something organised soon. I’d really like to do a solo camping trip and I’ve started thinking about what I’d need to take. This got me thinking about how much stuff I can fit in my US30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorbike Camping – Best Tent?</title>
      <link>/2019/08/sportsbike-camping-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 11:57:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/08/sportsbike-camping-trip/</guid>
      <description>I am an avid camper and rider but only recently began mixing the two. Camping for me is historically been large tents and lots of gear – cooking equipment, entertainment; everything I thought I could ever possibly need would get chucked into the back of the estate car and off we went.
However that’s not really viable when you’re on two wheels. Space is a premium so gear must be slimmed down and match the required criteria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to load your Sportbike - Best Luggage Options</title>
      <link>/2018/05/how-to-load-your-bike/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 21:57:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/how-to-load-your-bike/</guid>
      <description>And why tail packs are my go to..
lot of people&amp;rsquo;s first point of call for touring or long trips away would be a big, upright touring bike with hard panniers and a large top box. With lots of space for stowing away items that you may (or may not) need whilst your away. This is a fair point, but unless you are doing serious miles and several weeks away is this really necessary?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>